Knolls Action Project; Records apap105
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administration and Publicity, 1969-1994; 1; 3.0 cubic ft.
  - 11A. Notes, 1979; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 11A)
    Handwritten notes concerning the groups activities, calendar of events, and brainstorming lists. Also includes reports on KAPL safety and protocol. These notes may have belonged to Mike Baum and/or John Ragusa.
  - Organizing Guidelines, 1980 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 12)
  - Outreach (Originals), 1990 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 13)
  - Outreach Letters, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 14)
  - Phonathon Information, 1987-1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1982 April-1988 August; 1991 September; 1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 16)
  - Radioactive Waste - Yankee Rowe Shipments, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 17)
  - Radioactive Waste Demonstration (directions, letter, participants), 1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 18)
  - Radioactive Waste Demonstration (leaflets/slogans), 1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 19)
  - Radioactive Waste Demonstration Press Coverage, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 20)
  - Radioactive Waste Transport Meetings (Ballston Spa School District), 1990-1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 21)
    Includes minutes of school board meetings, hand-written notes, and correspondence regarding nuclear waste transport activities conducted by KAPL on the rail siding adjacent to the Malta Avenue Elementary School.
  - Radioactive Waste Transport Meetings (Saratoga County), 1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 22)
    Correspondence regarding meetings with Ballston Spa Village Board of Trustees, Saratoga County Board of Supervisors.
  - Railroad Maps, 1993 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 23)
  - Resources - Books, 1980s; 1991 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 24)
  - Resources - Films, Videos, 1982; 1986-1989; 1992-1994 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook - 1988 Civil Disobedience (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 26)
    Contains clippings, leaflets, copies of letters dealing with 1988 action.
  - Social Action Center (SAC) Meetings, 1982-1988 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 27)
  - Social Justice Center (SJC), 1991 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 28)
    Participating groups, SJC policy, minutes from August 19, 1991 meeting.
  - Song Sheet, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 29)
    Radioactive shipment.
  - Staff Reports, 1991 September-1992 June (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 30)
    Weekly activity reports of Daniel Mackay.
  - Tabling/Fundraising Supplies, 1991-1993 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 31)
    Resource catalogs.
  - USS Albany, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 32)
    Leaflets, flyers, clippings, press releases, actions protesting the naming of a nuclear sub after the city of Albany.
  - USS Albany, 1990 (Box 3 (1-Administration and Publicity), Folder 33)
    Protest of USS Albany's commissioning. Documentation expressing opposition of clergy to USS Albany.
- Activist Organizations, 1982-1994; 2; 1.0 cubic ft.
  KAP collected flyers and newsletters from many organizations. This series is a collection of information from other grassroots organizations involved in the anti-nuclear movement, including Citizens Awareness Network (CAN), Citizens' Environmental Coalition (CEC), Economic Conversion Council, INFACT, Nukewatch, Physicians for Social Responsibility (PSR). Information about activist organizations involved in military resistance can be found in Series 7.
  - Citizen Alert, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 1)
    Citizen Alert Native American Program.
  - Citizen Soldier: On Guard, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 2)
  - Citizens Awareness Network (CAN), 1991; 1992; 1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 3)
    Correspondence between Daniel Mackay and Dale MacLeod of CAN documenting their attempts to gain support from New York and Massachusetts Attorneys General in opposing the installation of a new atomic reactor at KAPL.
  - Citizens Clearinghouse for Hazardous Waste (CCHW), 1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 4)
    Contains two journals entitled Everyone's Backyard.
  - Citizens' Environmental Coalition (CEC), 1992; 1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 5)
  - Coalition to Stop Trident, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 6)
  - Community Action Against Racism and Violence, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 7)
  - Concerned Citizens for Nuclear Safety (CCNS), 1994; 1995 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 8)
    Contains the Nuclear Reactor, newsletter of CCNS, and two copies of Labwatch, newsletter of Los Alamos Study Group.
  - Economic Conversion Council, 1991 October-1993 December (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 9)
    Meeting minutes.
  - Energy Research Foundation, 1988; 1991-1993 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 10)
    Contains Research Updates and a copy of Rethinking Plutonium: A Review of Plutonium Operations in the U.S. Nuclear Weapons Complex.
  - G.E.: Brandywine Peace Community, 1982-1988 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 11)
    Contains newsletters and information related to Brandywine's protest of GE's development and production of systems for nuclear warfare. See oversize box for poster protesting GE.
  - Government Accountability Project (GAP), 1984-1988; 1990-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 12)
    Documents related to Whistleblower protection at DOE sites.
  - The Green Drummer, Nov/Dec 1993 to Nov/Dec 1994 - Newsletters, 1993 November-1994 December (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 13)
  - Ground Zero: Center for Nonviolent Action, 1985; 1991 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 14)
    Shipment of nuclear weapons and waste in the state of Washington.
  - Hanford Education Action League (HEAL), 1989 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 15)
    Contains The Hanford Journal and a Citizen's Guide to environmental restoration of Hanford. See oversize box for copies of HEAL newsletter Perspective (1990-1994).
  - INFACT, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 16)
    GE Boycott.
  - Institute for Energy and Environmental Research, (IEER), 1991-1993 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 17)
    Contains fact sheets, newsletters, workshop hand-outs.
  - MPN (Lobbying), 1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 18)
  - Misc. National: Center for Economic Conversion, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 19)
    Contains copies of publication Positive Alternatives.
  - Misc. National: Childhood Cancer Research Institute (CCRI), 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 20)
    Publications.
  - Misc. National:Economists Allied for Arms Reduction (ECAAR), 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 21)
    Contains newsletters, paper by William Weida entitled "Regional employment impacts from nuclear waste cleanup at Rocky Flats" (1992).
  - Misc. National:National Toxics Campaign (Military Toxics Project), 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 22)
    Newsletters.
  - Misc. National:The Nuclear Examiner, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 23)
    Newsletters of STAR-Save Texas Agriculture and Resources.
  - Misc. National: Peace Action (Don Gardner), 1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 24)
    Report from the Military Production Network winter 1994 meeting by Don Gardner, representing Peace Action and Texas Nuclear Responsibility Network.
  - Misc. National: Public Employees for Environmental Responsibility (PEER), 1993 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 25)
    Conference agenda.
  - Misc. National: Rocky Mountain Peace Center, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 26)
  - Native Americans for a Clean Environment (NACE), 1991-1992 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 27)
  - Nevada Nuclear Waste News, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 28)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Service (NIRS), 1994-1995 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 29)
  - Nukewatch: TruckWatch Materials, 1984-1992 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 30)
    Information on TruckWatch, the transportation of H-bombs and component parts in unmarked trucks by the DOE. Includes correspondence between Daniel Mackay and Bonnie Urfer of Nukewatch. See oversize box for copies of Pathfinder.
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility (PSR) - National and Local, 1988-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 31)
    Newsletters. Also contains papers documenting KAP's work with Capital District PSR chapter.
  - Radioactive Waste Campaign, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 32)
    Fact sheets, clippings.
  - Radioactive Waste Management Associates, 1991; 1992; 1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 33)
    Consultant Marvin Resnikoff.
  - Search (Nuclear Military Monitoring), 1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 34)
  - Snake River Alliance (SRA), 1991-1995 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 35)
    Newsletters and bulletins.
  - South Coast Against Nuclear Navies (SCANN)/England, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 36)
    Primarily newsletters.
  - Syracuse Peace Council Newsletter, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 37)
  - Tri-Valley CAREs: Citizen's Watch (newsletters), 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 38)
  - Trident Information Network (TIN), 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 39)
    Newsletters. Also, correspondence between Daniel Mackay and Stephen Kobasa of TIN.
  - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 40)
    Interview with Robert Pollard from The Monthly Planet.
  - War Resisters League (WRL), 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-Activist Organizations), Folder 41)
    See oversize folder for copies of the Nuclear Resister (1991-1994), information about and support for imprisoned anti-nuclear activists.
- Radioactive Waste Transport, 1978-1994; 3; 1.0 cubic ft.
  KAP was very concerned about the transport of radioactive waste. KAP formed an alliance with Nukewatch based in Wisconsin and the Snake River Alliance in Idaho to track the transport of spent reactor fuel from navy reactors at KAPL to INEL. Together they organized a network of waste tracking contacts located in each of the 10 states through which the waste traveled. This project is well documented and includes flyers, budget sheets, contacts, press coverage, and a diary of one particular train watcher.
  - DOD: RR Transport of Trident Missiles, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 1)
    Shipping documents.
  - DOE: DODX Shipments, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 2)
    Railroad records.
  - DOE: DODX Shipments, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 3)
  - DOE: DODX Shipments (Press), 1993-1994; clippings (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 4)
  - DOE: Shipyard Storage Naval Spent Fuel, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 5)
    Stort term environmental assessment conducted by the US Navy, and comments submitted by Daniel Mackay.
  - DOE: Spent Fuel Transport (misc), 1984-1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 6)
    Includes documents relating to shipment of radioactive waste to Idaho National Engineering Laboratory (INEL), and a DOE Environmental Assessment of the proposed adoption and implementation of a United States Policy on receipt and reprocessing of spent research reactor fuel (off-site fuels policy).
  - GAO: RR Safety Reports, 1989-1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 7)
  - GAO: Radiation Waste Transport Reports, 1988; 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 8)
  - KAPL/INEL, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 9)
    Includes information on KAPL and INEL, Position Paper regarding KAPL-INEL nuclear waste shipments, press releases regarding nuclear waste train watch.
  - KAPL: Radioactive Waste Transport, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 10)
  - KAPL: Summaries of Problems, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 11)
    See also oversize box for Schenectady Gazette series on KAPL.
  - NRP: M-140 Navy Fuel Cask Specs, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 12)
  - NRP: M-160 Naval Fuel Cask Specs, 1987; 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 13)
  - NRP: Naval Fuel Cask Specs, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 14)
  - NRP: RR Transport Accidents, 1982-1987 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 15)
  - NWTW: Activist Contacts, 1990; 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 16)
  - NWTW: Budget Sheets, 1992; 1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 17)
  - NWTW: INFACT, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 18)
  - NWTW: Northeast Activist Network, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 19)
  - NWTW: Northeast Press Coverage, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 20)
    See also oversize box for copies of Pathfinder and Nonviolent Activist.
  - NWTW: Nuclear Waste Track Watch (intro), 1990-1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 21)
  - NWTW: Nuclear Waste Track Watch (overview, route notes), 1978-1979; 1989-1990; 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 22)
  - NWTW: Nukewatch, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 23)
    Includes early correspondence between Daniel Mackay and Bonnie Urfer of Nukewatch organizing a joint action to monitor shipments.
  - NWTW: Press 1993 - Clippings (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 24)
  - NWTW: Press Contacts, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 25)
  - NWTW: Press Releases, 1992 August-1992 October (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 26)
  - NWTW: RR Route Maps, 1987; 1992; 1995 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 27)
  - NWTW: Snake River Alliance (SRA), 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 28)
    Joint action with KAP and Nukewatch.
  - NWTW: Train Watch Diary, 1992 August-1992 December (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 29)
    Diary sent by Ann Sorenson to Daniel Mackay.
  - NWTW: Union Pacific RR Manifest, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 30)
  - NWTWP: Graphics/Maps, Undated (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 31)
  - Nuclear Materials Transport: Regs, [Undated] (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 32)
  - Nukewatch: Midwest Press Coverage, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 33)
    Copies of Pathfinder.
  - Radioactive Waste Transport: General Issues, [Undated] (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 34)
    Contains only the name of one shipper.
  - Radioactive Waste Transport: State and Tribal Emergency Response, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 35)
  - SRA: NWTW Idaho Press Coverage, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 36)
    See oversize folder for poster "The Low Down Radioactive Waste - Train Blues Dance".
  - SRA: NWTW Idaho Press Coverage (copies), 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 37)
  - SRA: NWTW Idaho Press Coverage (copies), 1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 38)
    See oversize folder for original copies of Pathfinder.
  - Spent Fuel Transport, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 39)
    Miscellaneous, handwritten notes, earlier clippings.
  - Three Mile Island (TMI): Waste Transport, 1981-1988 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 40)
  - Trident II Nuclear Missile Railway Shipping Routes, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 41)
  - Trident Rocket Motor Shipping Hazards, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 42)
    Report presented to Michael Honda, Supervisor, Santa Clara Board of Supervisors by Glen Milner.
  - U.S.N.: Newport News Shipbuilding, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Radioactive Waste Transport), Folder 43)
    Contains clippings. Also, testimony of James Burritt, General Manager of Newport News Industrial Corporation, before the House Committee on Science, Space and Technology. Hearing topic: Spent fuel containers.
- Department of Energy (DOE), 1973-1994; 4; 2.0 cubic ft.
  Since the 1940's, DOE has been involved in the research, testing and production of nuclear weapons. Facilities supporting that effort generated large quantities of radioactive and hazardous materials which resulted in contamination of many of the facilities and surrounding areas. Series 4 includes information on these facilities and subsequent efforts of DOE to clean up and modernize the nuclear weapons complex. Box 1 contains facilities overviews, including the Final Report on DOE Nuclear Facilities by the Advisory Committee on Nuclear Facility Safety to the Secretary of Energy (November, 1991). It also includes information on environmental restoration, the process by which contaminated sites and facilities are identified and contamination is contained or removed. Box 2 contains information on individual DOE facilities.
  - DOE: Atomic Vapor Laser Isotope Separation (AVLIS), 1991 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 1)
  - DOE: Environmental Restoration, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 2)
    DOE plan to clean up the environment at its defense sites. Includes transcript of Environmental Restoration and Waste Management Advisory Committee public meeting in Colorado.
  - DOE: Environmental Restoration - Environmental Restoration and Waste Management (ERWM) Advisory Committee materials, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 3)
  - DOE: Environmental Restoration - Environmental Restoration and Waste Management (ERWM) Advisory Committee public meeting, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 4)
    Transcript and minutes.
  - DOE: Environmental Restoration - "The Dirt in the USDOE's Nuclear Waste Clean-up Budget", 1991 July (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 5)
    An investigation by Heart of America Northwest Research Center.
  - DOE: Environmental Restoration - Environmental Management - Readers Guide prepared by DOE, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 6)
  - DOE: Environmental Restoration - Priority System, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 7)
  - DOE: Environmental Restoration and Waste Management - 5-Year Plan, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 8)
  - DOE: Facilities Overview, 1988; 1990-1991 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 9)
  - DOE: Facilities Overview (Acronyms, Glossary), 1988; 1991-1994 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 10)
    Contains clippings, copies of DOE News, DOE media releases, and the following reports: "New Directions in Nuclear Safety Management and Organization" (DOE), "Final Report on DOE Nuclear Facilities: (Advisory Committee on Nuclear Facility Safety to the Secretary of Energy), "White Elephants: The expensive failures of the U.S. Department of Energy" (Natural Resources Defense Council), "Department of Energy Nuclear Weapons Complex" (Physicians for Social Responsibility).
  - DOE: Facilities Overview - Final Report on DOE Nuclear Facilities, 1991 November (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 11)
    A report by the Advisory Committee on Nuclear Facility Safety to the Secretary of Energy.
  - DOE: Facilities Overview - Final report of the Secretary of Energy Advisory Board Task Force on Radioactive Waste Management (draft), 1992 December (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 12)
    Includes two 1993 GAO reports, "DOD Budget: Future years defense program needs details based on comprehensive review", and "Department of Energy: Management problems require a long-term commitment to change".
  - DOE: Fernald Residents for Environmental Safety and Health (F.R.E.S.H.) Newsletters, 1992- 1994 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 13)
  - DOE: PEIS Reconfiguration, 1989; 1991-1993 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 14)
    Several reports regarding the Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement (PEIS) for the DOE's Environmental Restoration and Waste Management program (for reconfiguring, or modernizing, the nuclear weapons complex).
  - DOE: PEIS Reconfiguration Scope Hearings, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 15)
  - DOE: Public Involvement Guidelines, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 16)
  - DOE: Publications - Office of Technology Assessment, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 17)
    Publications regarding clean-up of the nuclear weapons complex.
  - DOE: Whistleblowers, 1988-1993 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 18)
    Articles and clippings on whistleblowers at DOE facilities.
  - DOE: "The Wrong Stuff" - An information summary on Victor Stello, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 19)
    Report by the Government Accountability Project on the Assistant Secretary for Defense Programs Designate.
  - Correspondence with KAPL employees, 1980-1989; 1991 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 1)
  - DOE: Hanford, 1988-1989; 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 2)
    See oversize box for special report of Moscow Pullman Daily News on "Hanford: Bombs to Boondoggle".
  - DOE: INEL, 1986-1988; 1990-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 3)
  - DOE: INEL (Reports), 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 4)
    Includes a Citizens guide to the Idaho National Engineering Laboratory compiled for the Environmental Defense Institute, two GAO Reports on Nuclear Health and Safety at INEL.
  - DOE: Lawrence Livermore Labs, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 5)
    Includes information on Edward Teller, co-founder of Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory.
  - DOE: Los Alamos Labs, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 6)
    Includes a conference report from LANL 2000: The role of the National Laboratory in the 21st Century (Aug. 20-22, 1993), and A Citizen's Guide to Los Alamos National Laboratory compiled by Concerned citizens for Nuclear Safety.
  - DOE: Oak Ridge, 1989; 1991; 1992 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 7)
    Includes A Citizen's Guide to Oak Ridge compiled by Oak Ridge Environmental Peace Alliance.
  - DOE: Paducah Gaseous Diffusion Plant, 1993; clippings (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 8)
  - DOE: Pantex, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 9)
    Includes several copies of The Nuclear Examiner, and a draft copy of the "Environmental Assessment for interim storage of plutonium components at Pantex" prepared by DOE.
  - DOE: Piketon, 1991-1993; clippings (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 10)
  - DOE: Pinellas, 1991; clippings (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 11)
  - DOE: Portsmouth Gaseous Diffusion Plant, 1984; 1991-1995 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 12)
    Includes several copies of "Environmental Restoration", a fact sheet prepared by DOE, as well as information obtained by Daniel Mackay during a 1995 visit to the Portsmouth Gaseous Diffusion Plant. See oversize box for original Special Section from the Portsmouth Daily Times, Sunday, Sept. 25, 1994: "Celebrating 40 years of Portsmouth Gaseous Diffusion Plant".
  - DOE: Rocky Flats, 1988; 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 13)